[Music]
[音乐]
yeah we made it
是的，我们做到了
alright so hi everybody my name is Josh
好吧，大家好，我叫乔希
this is Julian I work on the spring team
这是朱利安，我在春季队工作
right good to see you all how are you
很高兴见到大家
I'm just before we get too far down the
我只是在我们走得太远之前
line I mean I'm always curious how many
行，我是说我总是很好奇
of you are using spring ok good
你们中的人使用弹簧还可以
how many of you using a cloud platform
你们中有多少人使用云平台
like azure ok good ok right on you're
就像天蓝色，好，好，就在你身上
going with using well who's using Azure
很好地使用谁在使用Azure
in particular ok good okay so the rest
特别好的，好的，好的，其余的
will be converters ok if you have
如果有的话，将是转换器确定
questions oh oh very important very
问题哦哦非常重要非常
important before I get too far here
在我走到这里之前很重要
there's that code ok
那里的代码还可以
so we're about to write a lot of code
所以我们要写很多代码
together today we have very little time
今天在一起我们很少时间
together unfortunately but during this
不幸的是在一起
time we're gonna look at a lot of things
时候我们要看很多东西
and as always the goal is not to
和往常一样，目标不是
remember what has been typed it's more
记住输入的内容更多
to appreciate what is possible we're
欣赏我们有可能
gonna look at stuff in Azure and we're
要看Azure中的东西，我们
gonna then look at how that stuff is
然后看看那东西是怎么
supported by api's in the spring
在春季由api支持
community now I I've been a big fan of
现在，我一直是社区的忠实粉丝
what Microsoft is doing for spring users
微软为春季用户所做的工作
for a long time right they have been
很长时间以来，他们一直
using they have been building
使用他们已经建立
integrations for spring developers for
春季开发人员的集成
the last at least two and a half years
最近至少两年半
that I've been working with him right
我一直在和他一起工作
and there's teams in in in Redmond right
在雷蒙德有团队
there's teams in China and Shanghai
在中国和上海有团队
right so it's very interesting to me
对，所以对我来说很有趣
there's actually full-time there's
实际上有全职
actually a full-time team with lots of
实际上是一个全职团队，
people working on support for Spring at
为Spring工作的人们
Microsoft which i think is really cool
我认为微软真的很棒
right so so they've worked very closely
对，所以他们已经非常紧密地合作
with the spring team and there the goal
与春季队，那里的目标
is to make their integrations as easy to
使他们的集成变得容易
use and as palatable for spring
用作春天的美味
developers as possible and so there's
开发者，所以有
actually you know there's some really
其实你知道有些
big pieces that are already there right
大块已经存在的权利
and and I think I was always kind of an
而且我想我一直都是
interesting interesting thing as well
有趣的也是有趣的事情
right now in the world it's the number
现在在世界上
two most widely host platform right most
最合适的两个最广泛的主机平台
wide to use cloud so being able to
广泛使用云，因此能够
right code for that I think it's kind of
正确的代码，我认为这是
interesting how many of you know about
有趣的是，你们当中有多少人知道
Satya Nadella the CEO right very
萨蒂亚·纳德拉（Satya Nadella）首席执行官很对
interesting person he since he took over
自从他接手以来有趣的人
the whole you know the motivations for
整体上你知道动机
Microsoft have seemed to have changed
微软似乎已经改变
first of all they they have moved away
首先，他们已经搬走了
from this idea that Windows the desktop
从Windows桌面的想法开始
is the most important hub in the
是最重要的枢纽
universe and they're in there sort of
宇宙，他们在那里
embraced this idea that it doesn't
接受了这样的想法
matter who built the hub as long as they
谁建造了枢纽，只要他们
as long as they own it right and so no
只要他们拥有正确的权利，所以没有
that's very reasonable it's very
这是非常合理的
pragmatic so there was a friend of mine
务实所以我有一个朋友
a guy named Xavier soltero he created a
一个叫Xavier soltero的家伙，他创造了一个
Microsoft he created an app whose name I
微软，他创建了一个应用程序，其名称为
forget now because it was years ago
现在忘记，因为那是几年前
Microsoft bought that app for iOS that
微软为iOS购买了该应用，
was the number one email client on iOS
是iOS上排名第一的电子邮件客户端
right so people were using it on iOS
对，所以人们在iOS上使用它
more than Apple Mail he bought that
他买的比Apple Mail还要多
company and that technology and they
公司和那个技术，他们
just they just rebranded it Microsoft
只是他们只是将其更名为Microsoft
Outlook for iOS right very smart so I
iOS版Outlook非常聪明，所以我
saw that years ago I'm like oh I get it
几年前看到的我就像哦，我明白了
now they just want to be and they just
现在他们只是想成为，他们只是
want to control them the platform that's
想要控制他们的平台
fine right that's what everybody wants
好的权利，这就是每个人都想要的
to do same thing for Azure there there
为那里的Azure做同样的事情
it doesn't have to be Windows desktop it
它不必是Windows桌面
doesn't even have to be Windows on Azure
甚至不必是Azure上的Windows
as long as they control all right so
只要他们控制好
they didn't very sort of open now right
他们现在不太开放
and so this is what is it now it's
所以这就是现在的样子
already already more than half of the
已经超过一半了
app instances on Azure are now Linux and
Azure上的应用程序实例现在是Linux
dollar and non Windows right and that's
美元和非Windows权利，那就是
a very interesting sort of situation so
一种非常有趣的情况，所以
when I see that kind of happens kind of
当我看到这种情况时
stuff happening when I see friends like
当我看到喜欢的朋友时发生的事情
Xavier who who's from SpringSource right
来自SpringSource的Xavier是谁
xavier worked on IP rick and and all
xavier从事IP rick等工作
these things back in the spring source
这些东西回到了春天
day so to see him go to Microsoft and
那天见他去微软，
see people like that go to Microsoft
看到这样的人去微软
they're now Julianne yeah there you go
他们现在是朱莉安娜，是的，你去了
it's a it's a long journey I don't see a
这是一段漫长的旅程，我看不到
lot of smart people going there so so
很多聪明人去那里
for me to engage the government then I
让我参与政府
I'm happy
我很高兴
why go why I work on a secondary team
为什么去，为什么我在二级团队工作
working on the spring when I can just
我可以在春天工作的时候
work on spring but but either way lots
在春季工作，但无论如何
of good stuff there so I've spent a lot
那里有很多好东西，所以我花了很多钱
of time working with people on the on
与人一起工作的时间
the mic
麦克风
side of the deal right so we just had
交易的一面，所以我们只是
Teresa nuyen and Kylie being for example
例如，Teresa nuyen和Kylie
on my podcast a bootiful podcast they
在我的播客上，一个可悲的播客
were from Microsoft as well so bootiful
同样来自微软
podcast how many of you listen to
播客你们中有多少人听
podcasts okay how many of listen to my
播客好吧，有多少听我的
podcast the only one that matters okay
播客中唯一重要的一个
the rest of you get on there you go
其余的人去那里
bootiful podcasts on iTunes and Google
iTunes和Google上可疑的播客
Play so we had people from we had
玩所以我们有来自我们的人
interviews with them I did a I did this
与他们的访谈我做了一个我做了这个
blog bootiful oh yes I did this blog
博客不错，是的，我做了这个博客
series last year and it was very very
去年的系列，这非常非常
popular it's one of the more popular
它是最受欢迎的之一
things that we've done it's a six-part
我们所做的事情分为六个部分
series to using Azur and spring and so
系列使用Azur和spring等
on together so like that that
这样在一起
relationship is very very interesting to
关系是非常非常有趣的
me and some of my friend Julian here you
我和我的一些朋友朱利安（Julian）在这里
don't you don't know anything about
难道你一无所知
spring you know what I mean what are you
春天你知道我的意思你是什么
doing since then just ask her or else so
从那以后做就问她吧
so you're now at Microsoft yeah I do
所以你现在在微软，是的
one way to go right but gay hipster has
一种正确的方法，但同性恋时髦有
always had a good sort of innovation
总是有很好的创新
right yeah it's working really good
是的，它工作得很好
because good right okay
因为好吧好吧
so that's very cool so that's we're
所以非常酷，这就是我们
going to talk about today now how do you
现在要谈论今天你如何
get started with Ezra how do you sign up
Ezra入门如何注册
for a new account for people who are
为那些
haven't done this yet yeah okay
还没有做到这一点，好吧
so portable desert calm I said okay
这么轻便的沙漠风平浪静我说好
usually but six $200 of food credits
通常，但有6张$ 200的食品抵免额
okay and what is that in like that's
好的，那是什么意思
right yeah those are tons of free stuff
是的，这些都是大量的免费物品
for always you know like free cheers do
永远都知道，就像自由的欢呼一样
you have unlimited accounts at Microsoft
您在Microsoft拥有无限帐户
for me yeah I can
对我来说，我可以
yeah I do a pivotal so you should come
是的，我很重要，所以你应该来
to pit oh that's not much at the sewer
加油哦，下水道不多
you know we have it anyway you know
你知道我们有吗你知道
right um okay so we have like so that
好的，好吧，我们有这样的
you can start up there and there's a lot
你可以在那里开始，那里有很多
of interesting things that I think for
我认为有趣的事情
me that make up Microsoft Azure oh great
组成Microsoft Azure的我，太好了
obviously what we're going to talk about
显然我们要谈论的是
today is writing spring apps that talk
今天正在写春天的应用程序
to infrastructure that's managed by
到由
Azure and I think that's really one of
我认为Azure确实是其中之一
the key differentiators there right you
关键的区别因素就在那里
can run code foundry on Microsoft Azure
可以在Microsoft Azure上运行代码代工厂
we were named pivotal and cut funding
我们被任命为关键和削减资金
particular we're named partner of the
特别是我们被称为
year for Microsoft last year the year
微软去年的一年
before I forget because so many people
在我忘记之前，因为有那么多人
generate you know large customers huge
让您知道大客户庞大
customers that come to piddle they want
来讨价还价的客户
to run their workloads in the cloud but
在云中运行他们的工作负载，但是
they want that layer beneath them that
他们想要在他们下面的那一层
allows them to move to another cloud if
允许他们移动到另一个云，如果
they need to a lot of these are people
他们需要很多这些人
that are like well AWS you know I've
就像我知道的AWS
seen what happens when people run
看到人们跑步时会发生什么
applications on AWS right they end up
最终在AWS上运行的应用程序
competing with eight Amazon right Amazon
与八个亚马逊竞争亚马逊
somebody starts building a business so
有人开始做生意，所以
if you're successful or native yes a lot
如果您是成功人士或本地人，则很多
of people like I don't want to risk that
像我这样的人不想冒险
or maybe they're in the same market as
也许他们与
eight of us right so they're they're
我们八个正确的，所以他们是
doing retail or something like that and
做零售之类的
they don't want to pay Amazon more money
他们不想付给亚马逊更多钱
so they go to they're looking for a good
所以他们去找一个好东西
option but they're they're a little
选择，但他们是他们有点
they're not excited about a Davis and
他们对戴维斯并不感到兴奋，
the technology is not you know what they
技术不是你知道他们是什么
need they can get elsewhere right and
需要他们可以正确地到达其他地方
they also want portability right they
他们也想要便携性
want to go to say okay well Microsoft's
想说很好，微软的
got all these really great things but a
得到了所有这些非常伟大的东西，但是
lot of organizations want multi data
许多组织想要多数据
center strategies so they go to things
集中战略，以便他们去做事
like Cloud Foundry so we have a great
像Cloud Foundry，所以我们有一个很棒的
sort of partnership with Microsoft and
与Microsoft和
as a result a lot of people use that on
结果是很多人在
Azure and so I thought that was kind of
Azure，所以我认为这有点
interesting and you can run it on there
有趣，你可以在那里运行它
you can run it on kubernetes and there's
您可以在kubernetes上运行它，
a Azur aks a kubernetes service
Azur aks a kubernetes服务
you could also there's also a weird
你也可以有一个怪异的
thing where you can like it's the azure
你可以喜欢的东西是蔚蓝
web
网络
yeah that's a thing yeah yeah there's a
是的，是的，是的，有一个
there's options okay but the point is
有很多选择，但是重点是
that's not what we're gonna talk about
那不是我们要谈论的
that because that's all sort of either
那是因为要么
it's not what I would recommend which is
这不是我建议的
like the fabric fabric is fine but why
像面料面料很好，但是为什么
would you do that instead of something
你会代替那件事吗
like kubernetes or class I agree and
像kubernetes或我同意的课程，
then that's all that's all good but
那就是所有的一切，但是
what's interesting about Azure is all
关于Azure的所有有趣之处就是全部
this other stuff all this stuff that I
其他所有这些东西，我
don't want to manage right all this
不想管理所有这一切
stuff and I'm not interested in managing
东西，我对管理不感兴趣
like infrastructure so what we're gonna
像基础设施，所以我们要
do is going to build some software today
今天要做的是构建一些软件
it talks to these different things and
谈到这些不同的东西，
we'll introduce how to create them what
我们将介绍如何创建它们
we're not gonna do is create them on the
我们不会做的是在
fly though so if you've ever seen talks
飞，所以如果你曾经看过谈话
that I do
我做的
I don't usually spend a lot of time
我通常不会花很多时间
doing any one particular thing in my
在我的身上做任何一件特别的事情
presentations but with uh sewer you know
演讲，但有下水道，你知道
and with any cloud provider not just as
并与任何云提供商一起
you were obviously it takes time you
你显然是需要时间的
have to provision infrastructure and so
必须提供基础设施等等
I don't want to sit here waiting five
我不想坐在这里等五个
minutes making a cup of tea while my
分钟喝一杯茶，而我的
infrastructure spins up is that five
基础设施旋转是五个
minutes but it's still longer than I
分钟，但仍然比我长
want to wait so we're gonna I've already
想等待，所以我们已经
got rabbits up my sleeve you know that
把兔子拉上我的袖子，你知道
expression you see a magic trick and you
表达你看到一个魔术，你
got a rabbit up your sleeve so we're
袖子上有只兔子，所以我们
gonna build new software today and of
今天将要开发新软件
course in order to do this we'll go here
为了做到这一点，我们会去这里
to my second favorite place on the
到我第二个最喜欢的地方
internet after production start that
生产后的互联网开始
spring today oh let me um let me see
今天春天哦，让我，让我看看
here get status good definitely not
在这里获得地位肯定不是
gonna commit that I we're doing the
承诺我在做
slides I think we're done anybody have
幻灯片，我认为我们已经完成任何人
any questions about the slides okay
关于幻灯片的任何问题都可以
moving on good downloads good all right
继续进行良好的下载，一切顺利
so there's nothing there except that
所以那里除了
poop from the OS so we're gonna go
从操作系统大便，所以我们要去
through application we're just gonna use
通过应用程序，我们将使用
a lasting latest stable thing I'm going
我要去的持久的最新稳定事物
to call this Azur and we're gonna bring
叫这个阿祖尔，我们要带
in the support that we need to build
在我们需要建立的支持中
applications today using my stuff's Azur
今天使用我的东西的应用程序
so I'm gonna bring in the web support I
所以我要加入网络支持
want Lombok I want to Microsoft sequel
想要龙目岛，我想要微软的续集
server I think I can see wanting to
服务器，我想我可以看到想要
connect to Microsoft sequel server we
连接到Microsoft续集服务器
app we have but we have Microsoft sequel
应用，但我们有微软续集
server support on the spring initializer
Spring初始化程序上的服务器支持
right because there's such a such a huge
对，因为有这么大
demand right I'd to be honest with you I
要求权利我要对你诚实
didn't appreciate
不欣赏
I didn't know I didn't appreciate before
我不知道我以前没有欣赏过
our partnership with him just how
我们与他的伙伴关系如何
popular sequel server is I always
流行的续集服务器是我一直
thought it was just sort of like all
认为这就像所有
Oracle and then like postcodes in my
甲骨文，然后喜欢我的邮政编码
sequel i yeah but yeah and but a sequel
续集我是的，但是的，但是一个续集
server is awesome right and I'm glad to
服务器很棒，我很高兴
see that it's very popular so we added
看到它非常受欢迎，所以我们添加了
it to the initializer and today you know
它到初始化程序，今天你知道
you saw the keynote I think we probably
您看到了主题演讲，我想我们可能
heard about r2 EBC is that true our 2d
听说r2 EBC是真的我们的2d
VCS are reactive a API for sequel data
VCS是反应式的续集数据API
store access you can use sequel server
可以使用续集服务器进行存储访问
both reactively and nonreactive Lee
反应性和非反应性李
right so it's actually really it's ahead
对，所以实际上它真的在前面
of Oracle good thing right when you get
获得Oracle产品的好处
your pub right so so all that stuff
你的酒吧吧，所以所有的东西
we're going to add that we're gonna add
我们要添加的是，我们要添加
that they're gonna use JDBC and then we
他们将使用JDBC，然后我们
need to Azure we need the dependencies
需要Azure我们需要依赖项
for our server so we're gonna bring in a
为我们的服务器，所以我们要带一个
few of the different dependencies I
几个不同的依赖我
think we're gonna use Azure support
认为我们将使用Azure支持
though we just need one really right we
虽然我们只需要一个真的
just need one that will bring in the
只需要一个会带来
dependency management that manages the
依赖管理
versions of these maven plug-in maybe
这些Maven插件的版本可能
dependencies and with that we can then
依赖关系，然后我们就可以
just bring in the other dependencies
只是引入其他依赖
that we need so we've only got a few
我们需要的，所以我们只有几个
checkboxes here there's way more options
复选框，这里有更多选择
than there are checkboxes okay anything
比有复选框好吗
else can you demo
否则你可以演示
yeah I haven't used it no you can do oh
是的，我没用过，你可以做哦
yeah okay good well bring keep on good
是的，很好，很好，请继续保持良好
we got a new demo oh good so we're gonna
我们有一个新的演示哦，很好，我们要
go hit generate in my account okay so
去打在我的帐户中生成好吧，所以
I'm gonna open this up okay
我要打开这个好
and while we're there
而当我们在那里
how do I provision key vault oh just I
我该如何设置密钥库
think keyboard okay
认为键盘还可以
Oh still it's okay okay one okay
哦，还好吧，好吧，一个好吧
beautiful yes beautiful month
美丽是美丽的一个月
oh yeah he's now on Windows yes awesome
哦，是的，他现在在Windows上很棒
I looked at the new surface pro that's
我看着新的Surface Pro
pretty interesting I booted should let's
我启动的很有趣，应该让我们
go for myself
自己去
Pro yeah I want the big one like okay
亲，我要大个子好吗
thank you I keep a web serie cluster in
谢谢，我在保留一个网络系列
there it's yeah it's a very fat jar yeah
是的，这是一个非常胖的罐子，是的
okay so we've got this now create a key
好的，现在我们已经创建了一个密钥
vault yeah okay would you follow uh-huh
保险柜是的，您可以跟随吗
uh-huh uh-huh
嗯嗯嗯
good and choose a resource group exists
好，选择一个资源组存在
oh yes so it's a choice we carry for
哦，是的，这是我们的选择
we're gonna just let this run in the
我们要让它在
background yeah and we could oh yeah so
背景是的，我们可以哦是的，所以
people can see well yeah we'll do that
人们可以看到很好，是的，我们会做到的
again slow note okay so it's refreshing
再次慢音好，所以令人耳目一新
well it's good that's a little bit you
好吧，那只是你一点
never know yeah deployment failed okay
永远不知道是的，部署失败了吗
so maybe we already nine News oh you
所以也许我们已经有九个新闻哦
already did it
已经做了
we should have refresh the first time so
我们应该在第一时间刷新
he votes there it is yeah okay go to the
他在那里投票，是的，可以
resource so the first ones ready and I
资源，所以第一个准备好了，我
tell you the second one sweet okay so
告诉你第二个，好吧，所以
you can show that later right okay so
您可以稍后再显示，好吧
what we're gonna do is we're gonna build
我们要做的是建立
an application that takes advantage of
利用以下优势的应用程序
all this stuff we've got a brand new
所有这些东西，我们有一个全新的
build here in order for this to work we
为了在这里建造，我们要在这里工作
need to add
需要添加
more dependencies right so let's go
正确的更多依赖关系，让我们开始吧
ahead and we're gonna add some
前面，我们要添加一些
dependencies here and I think the first
依赖在这里，我认为第一个
thing I want to do is I want to look at
我想做的就是看
something that's boring something that
无聊的东西
you could do without Azur but that would
你可以不用Azur就能做到，但是那会
be much more difficult right one of
是更困难的权利之一
those examples is sequel server sequel
那些例子是续集服务器续集
server is again just a really
服务器再次只是一个真正的
interesting thing um
有趣的事情
again when I think about databases right
再一次，当我想到数据库的权利
I mean I think of like true
我的意思是我认为
enterprise-grade
企业级
databases if you ask me 15 years ago
数据库如果您15年前问我
which three databases can I guarantee
我可以保证哪三个数据库
would be a good fit for any organization
适合任何组织
I would say Oracle
我会说甲骨文
sorry Oracle db2 and sequel server these
对不起，Oracle db2和续集服务器这些
things the features enterprises need
企业需要的功能
like at rest encryption of data right
像静态数据加密一样
this idea that you can add data to a
您可以将数据添加到
database and have it be encrypted by the
数据库并由
database itself that guy you know
数据库本身，你认识的家伙
PostGIS has for example but these kinds
例如PostGIS，但这类
of things are very very useful so what
事情非常非常有用
we're gonna do is we're gonna use sequel
我们要做的是使用续集
server and I don't know if you've ever
服务器，我不知道你是否曾经
had to manage a sequel server database
必须管理续集服务器数据库
but it's not something that I enjoy
但这不是我喜欢的东西
doing in fact I would much prefer not to
实际上，我宁愿不要
do it although I guess it's now possible
尽管我想现在可以做到
to deploy on a Linux it's possible to
部署在Linux上，
run yeah it's a run you can run it on
是的，可以运行它
Linux out sequel server so the world is
Linux out续集服务器
different anyway you can great but the
无论如何，你都可以很棒，但是
point is I'm not gonna run it at all
关键是我根本不会运行它
it's just on a cloud now
现在只是在云上
so how gotten is I've got a sequel
所以我有续集
server instance I went to my I went to
我去的服务器实例
my home essentially and I search for
基本上是我的家，我在寻找
sequel server and then you can you can
续集服务器，那么你可以
see that there's sequel servers you
看到有续集服务器
create a server and then you create one
创建一个服务器，然后创建一个
of those and when you have a sequel
这些，当你有续集时
server then you create a database right
服务器，然后您创建一个数据库吧
so I've got sequel databases and then in
所以我有续集数据库，然后在
there I've got adventures now this is
我现在有冒险了
based on a template image okay
根据模板图片可以
provided by Azur it's just a template
由Azur提供，这只是一个模板
database called adventure or something
数据库称为冒险之类的
rather and then you've got tables in
相反，然后你有表
there so where's my tables where's my
那边我的桌子在哪儿
data browser data security there's a way
数据浏览器数据安全有一种方法
to view that data query editor that'll
查看该数据查询编辑器
work that looks right password what is
看起来正确的密码工作是什么
the password so I'm gonna okay maybe
密码，这样我就可以了
fair that's okay no problem
公平，没关系
nope so the nice thing about Azur is
不，所以关于Azur的好处是
that they have this thing called a
他们有这个东西叫做
resource group okay and so a resource
资源组还可以，所以资源
group you can you can create all these
小组你可以创建所有这些
manage infrastructure pieces and assign
管理基础架构并分配
them to a resource group and then when
他们到一个资源组，然后什么时候
you're done with your presentation on
您的演示文稿已经完成
stage you don't need the resource group
阶段，您不需要资源组
and everything that you created gets
您创建的所有内容都会得到
destroyed so I can show you passwords
销毁了，所以我可以告诉你密码
and I don't care you know it's all gonna
我不在乎你知道这一切都会
be gone in a minute anyway so grip
一分钟就走了所以抓紧
password
密码
okay so sequel soon so smart so it's
好吧，续集很快就这么聪明，这是
springtime okay so I'm gonna add this
春天好吧，我要添加这个
here I'm gonna log in hit OK and there's
在这里，我要登录，点击确定，
my database tables and I've got a bunch
我的数据库表，我有一堆
of tables already and you know I've got
已经有桌子了，你知道我有
a table called products so I can say
一个叫做产品的表，所以我可以说
select all from actually one if I can
如果可以的话，请从一个人中全选
just double click on bagel there's my
只需双击百吉饼，我的
schema right so select all from product
模式正确，因此从产品中全选
can I do that
我可以那样做吗
run whoops I need to specify the schema
运行whoops，我需要指定架构
sales OT that product ok so there you go
销售该产品还可以，所以您去了
you know it's pretty basic anybody here
你知道这是很基本的
use Microsoft Access or something like
使用Microsoft Access或类似的东西
that
那
in the browser really yeah but it's not
在浏览器中确实可以，但事实并非如此
made to work I am I used to be for two
上班我是我曾经两个
years yeah
年呀
[Music]
[音乐]
this is it
就是这个
there you go I truly believe this yes
你去那里我真的相信这是
like statistically most software out
统计上最喜欢的软件
there the competition is some homegrown
那里的比赛有些本土化
access or Microsoft Excel solution and I
访问或Microsoft Excel解决方案，我
mean how many of you have something
表示你们中有多少人有东西
written with a spreadsheet somewhere
用电子表格写在某处
that should be managed by software there
应该由那里的软件来管理
you go there's at least a few the rest
你走了，至少还有一些
of you are just too embarrassed or or
你们当中的人太尴尬了，或者
worse you don't know that it's happening
更糟糕的是你不知道它正在发生
but it is happening so I'm gonna bring
但它正在发生，所以我要带
in the sequel I'm going to connect to
在续集中，我要连接到
this database here I'm gonna use this
这个数据库我要用这个
query because we know it works
查询，因为我们知道它有效
and I'm just gonna the it's got a name a
我只是要给它起个名字
what is this message is it's a I guess I
这是什么消息，我猜我
want the Select name product number
想要选择名称产品编号
number and then it go all right there
数字，然后就可以了
you go that's a simple enough query okay
你去那是一个简单的查询好吗
so so let's let's now build our
所以让我们现在建立我们的
application and get it to work with that
应用程序并使其与之一起使用
so we're gonna go to our as our
所以我们要去当我们的
application and I'm gonna create a
应用程序，我要创建一个
component can you make can you see that
您可以制作组件吗，可以看到
fine is that too small make it a little
太小了一点就好了
larger font font make this 22 and I'm
较大的字体使这22和我
gonna say add component class sequel
要说添加组件类的续集
server demo okay an event listener
服务器演示好了，事件监听器
application ready event class public
应用就绪事件类公共
void talk - yeah whatever sequel server
空话-是的，无论是续集服务器
there you go and we're gonna do is want
你去那里，我们要做的就是
to inject the the JDBC template and how
注入JDBC模板以及如何
many of you've used the JDBC template
你们中的许多人已经使用了JDBC模板
before it's a very common anything I
在这很常见之前，我
think if you use spring 15 years ago the
想想如果你用15年前的春天
reason you got into it was probably
你进入它的原因可能是
because I I'm getting better okay like
因为我越来越好了
in the very beginning knows all about
从一开始就知道
this I would always just add the
这我总是会添加
constructor and you know whatever but
构造函数，你什么都不知道
but now I'm starting to like this Lombok
但是现在我开始喜欢这个龙目岛
annotation have you seen this before
注解你以前看过这个吗
Lombok allows you to synthesize a
龙目岛可让您合成
constructor you
构造你
say Jeeves 10% that query come on
说Jeeves 10％的查询来了
select I'm gonna take this query paste
选择我要将此查询粘贴
it in there okay and I'm gonna provide a
在那里，我要提供一个
row member so the row mapper
行成员，所以行映射器
and we're gonna create an object to type
我们将创建一个要输入的对象
what did we call this here it's called a
我们在这里称之为什么
product okay
产品还可以
so static not short static class product
所以静态不短静态类产品
private string number or name yeah and
私有字符串编号或名称，是的，
then private into number is that right
那么私有成数字是正确的
no strings as well a boutique number
没有字串，也没有精品店号码
right so number and let's map it in the
正确的数字，然后将其映射到
sequel but I'm gonna it's redundant
续集，但我会多余的
product that product number is City so
产品编号为市的产品
product that may impact that number it's
可能影响该数字的产品
okay so I'm gonna map it to a instance
好吧，我要映射到一个实例
of this product okay and there you go
这个产品好了，你去了
and what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna visit
我要做的就是去拜访
each product I'll say a new product
每个产品我都会说一个新产品
results set that get string the first
结果集首先获得字符串
field is the name as it capitals yeah
字段是大写的名称，是的
capital n and then the second one is the
大写字母n，然后第二个是
yeah product number okay
是的，产品编号还可以
and that should work that should give me
那应该工作，应该给我
a result like that okay so I'm gonna
这样的结果好吧，我要
visit each one of those results that
访问这些结果中的每一项，
come back I'll say for each and I just
回来，我会为每个人说，我只是
want to log it out now using my logger
想要现在使用我的记录器注销
which I'm gonna synthesized here using
我将在这里使用合成
log4j so there we go
log4j所以我们走了
log info now in order for this to work I
现在记录信息以使其正常工作
need to config that allows me to talk to
需要配置，使我可以与之交谈
a zoo or something it's just standard
动物园或只是标准的东西
spring dot data source type stuff right
弹簧点数据源类型的东西正确
I'm not gonna do anything special here
我不会在这里做任何特别的事情
so okay okay properties and data source
所以好吧好吧属性和数据源
there we go
我们去
paste okay so all I'm doing is I'm
粘贴好，所以我要做的就是
saying this is the password here's the
说这是密码，这是
password here's the URL the URL has a
密码，这是URL所在的URL
password in it keep that in mind so you
请记住其中的密码，以便您
need it twice for some reason you could
由于某种原因需要两次
probably get away with not having it
可能因为没有它而逃脱
here or not having it here maybe yeah I
在这里或没有在这里也许是的，我
haven't tried it but it should work yeah
还没有尝试过，但是应该可以
here we go go go go all right hey look
在这里，我们走吧，走吧，好吧，嘿，看
at that so there's our data okay so you
这样我们的数据就可以了
can see that was easy enough okay
可以看到这很容易
something that now we're just talking to
现在我们正在谈论的东西
sequel server big win but I don't think
续集服务器大获全胜，但我不认为
I mean yes you can use a xuer to manage
我的意思是，您可以使用xuer进行管理
sequel server and I think that's a win
续集服务器，我认为这是一个胜利
because you don't have to manage that
因为你不必管理
piece of infrastructure but if you're
基础设施，但如果您是
gonna use a platform if you've gotta use
如果您必须使用平台
something like Azure which is kind of
像Azure这样的东西
sticky there should be a really good
粘性应该真的很好
reason for it and a lot of people for
原因和很多人
what one of the things that I love about
我最喜欢的一件事
us is cosmos DB right so cosmos DB is a
我们是波斯菊数据库，所以波斯菊数据库是
piece of infrastructure that you can't
您无法做到的基础架构
get outside of azure it just runs in a
走出天蓝色，它只是在一个
sewer um and I was looking for some I
下水道，我正在寻找一些我
looked up and down I looked left and
上下看，我向左看
right I looked everywhere to find out
对，我四处寻找
about cosmos DB I was trying to find a
关于宇宙数据库，我试图找到一个
way for me to be able to say that I
让我能够说我的方式
would not use this right I was looking
不会使用我一直在寻找的权利
for a way to say this is not the right
用一种方式说这是不正确的
fit and I didn't have a lot of luck and
身体健康，我没有很多运气，
the reason is because first of all a
原因是因为首先
sewer has more data centers than any
下水道拥有比任何其他公司更多的数据中心
other cloud provider so there are no
其他云提供商，因此没有
there are more locations for Microsoft
微软有更多地点
Azure in the world than any other cloud
世界上的Azure比其他任何云
provider more more more geographic
供应商更多，更多地域
geographic locations did you know
你知道地理位置
there's even a sewer in China right
中国甚至还有下水道
that's very hard to do do you know freak
这很难做到吗？
out yeah China yeah it's how that
是的，中国，是这样的
because that's that's useful it's unique
因为那很有用，它是独一无二的
but it's not particularly hard from a
但这并不难
government perspective to get there to
政府的观点
have a region in China on the other hand
另一方面在中国有一个地区
is very difficult because of course what
当然很难，因为
happens if you're a public cloud
如果您是公共云，则会发生
provider in China right the first person
在中国提供服务的人是第一人
that says something bad about somebody
说某人不好
in the government if they deploy that
在政府，如果他们部署
app onto that region you know takes down
应用程式移至您所了解的区域
the whole cloud
整个云
right so that's a it's dangerous so they
对，所以这很危险，所以他们
have to make they have to be very very
必须使他们必须非常非常
careful about getting that deployed
小心部署
there and so it's actually a separate
在那里，所以实际上是一个单独的
it's not it's you can't manage it
不是因为你无法管理
exactly in the same way that you manage
完全按照您管理的方式
the rest of us who were it's actually a
我们其余的人实际上是
separate company technically but it
从技术上说是独立的公司
works right if you if you business
如果你做生意就可以正常工作
depends on being able to go to China
取决于能够去中国
that's there that's a big deal if you
如果你在那里那是很重要的
come here right sometimes this is China
来这里有时候是中国
property right yeah that's that's to me
产权，对，就是我
that's super violent right there you can
那是超级暴力
actually take your code that runs in the
实际使用您在
rest of the world and get it to go into
世界其他地方，并使其进入
a huge market you can't afford to ignore
您不能忽视的巨大市场
this market so so I was looking for
这个市场，所以我一直在寻找
reasons why well maybe I don't want to
为什么我不想的原因
use cosmos maybe there's something wrong
使用宇宙也许有什么问题
with it maybe it's too expensive turns
也许它太昂贵了
out it's not that if it's competitive
并不是说它是否具有竞争力
what about api compatibility with it
api与它的兼容性如何
what if it doesn't match my expectations
如果不符合我的期望怎么办
well it does actually match what I want
好，它确实符合我想要的
to do because you can use it like
之所以这样做，是因为您可以像
MongoDB you can use it like a sequel
MongoDB，您可以像续集一样使用它
database you can use it like Cassandra
数据库，您可以像Cassandra一样使用它
so there's a lot of different ways you
所以你有很多不同的方式
know what's a thing and we're going 1280
知道这是什么，我们要去1280
CDC portal so what is it etcb xcd and
CDC门户网站是什么，etcb xcd和
extremely are true to setup also right
设置极为正确
yeah there's like one unique thing that
是的，有一件独特的事情
just gets on with the SQL right right
刚开始就正确使用SQL
there's a lot you can it is one database
有很多可以的一个数据库
engine that has these different
具有这些不同的引擎
interfaces that you can use now that
您现在可以使用的界面
might sound a little crazy and it might
可能听起来有点疯狂，可能
make the question of well what does it
提出很好的问题是什么
actually do well it's a database it's a
实际上做得很好，这是一个数据库，这是一个
geographically replicated like database
地理复制像数据库
it works very very quickly when you use
当您使用时，它的工作非常非常快
it in sequel you know you can use your
它的续集，你知道你可以使用你的
queries against it there are sequel you
对它的查询有续集
don't update exactly using sequel but
不完全使用续集进行更新，但
still some very interesting options so
还有一些非常有趣的选择，所以
the point is if you're using it if you
关键是如果您正在使用它，如果您
want to use it you can use the low-level
想要使用它可以使用低级
API or you can use it from spring data
API或您可以从spring数据中使用它
so there's actually a module yeah
所以实际上有一个模块
synchronous up yeah right right No
同步向上是正确正确否
I think we're happy I like this one
我觉得我们很高兴我喜欢这个
works with screen data right let's do
使用屏幕数据吧
that that is synchronous right so the
那是同步的，所以
point is there's a whole spring data
重点是整个春天的数据
intubation and that's what we're gonna
插管，这就是我们要做的
show you here so I'm going to go back to
在这里告诉你，我要回去
my build and let's see here I'm gonna
我的构建，让我们看看这里
open up this project file to remember
打开该项目文件以记住
the build file ok did you do on the XML
确定文件，您对XML做了吗
okay and all I want is the version of by
好吧，我想要的是by的版本
the way if you're using Java 12 you're
如果您使用的是Java 12，
gonna need that draw anything greater
需要更大的吸引力
than 9 you'll eventually need this so
超过9，您最终将需要这个，所以
I'm just gonna go ahead and add this
我要继续添加
right now so Jack's be your little
现在，让杰克成为你的小孩子
justice oh yeah okay there's that and
正义哦，是的，那是和
then I want to bring in the the smoothie
那我要带冰沙
hey we go cosmos TV okay the starter so
嘿，我们去宇宙电视好了
here we are so I'm adding in the Asuma
我们在这里，所以我要加入阿苏玛
cosmos TV spring woot starter and again
宇宙电视弹簧再次吸引初学者
I don't have to manage the version
我不必管理版本
because that's already managed by this
因为这已经由这个来管理
spring bomb yeah familiar with the
春季炸弹，是的，熟悉
spindle status yeah you just import them
主轴状态是的，您只需导入它们
and you get everything automatic
你会自动得到一切
configuration is ready to be used
准备使用配置
right so what entities do we have in
是的，所以我们拥有什么实体
cosmos well we're gonna create it we
宇宙，我们要去创造它
have an object of type reservation I
有一个类型为reservation的对象
thought as much
想得太多
just making sure so it's a reservation
只是确保要预约
and we're going to have a document and
我们将有一个文档，
this is a call Microsoft Azure spring
这是一个电话Microsoft Azure春天
that at cosmos TV core mapping document
宇宙电视核心映射文件中的内容
okay
好的
[Music]
[音乐]
right alright good so a tidy
对，好，那么整洁
there's my entity okay so now I'm going
我的实体还可以，所以现在我要去
to persist this into the database I
坚持到我的数据库
won't be able to manage that the
将无法管理
lifecycle of it and so I'm going to use
它的生命周期，所以我要使用
a document DB repository okay
文档数据库存储库还可以
managing entities of type reservation
类型保留管理实体
whose primary keys of types of string
其主键为字符串类型
and that's it once I have this I can now
就这样，一旦我有了它，我现在就可以
create a cosmos DB demo okay so class
创建一个cosmos DB演示好，所以上课
cosmos DB demo event listener
cosmos DB演示事件侦听器
application or any event class public
应用程序或任何公共事件类
void cosmos sure component good stuff
无效的宇宙确保组件好东西
and in order to get this to work I'm
为了使这个工作，我
going to inject my reservation
要注入我的保留
repository like so and we're gonna say
像这样的仓库，我们要说
required arcs constructor and now I want
必需的弧线构造函数，现在我要
to write some data today base I'm going
今天要写一些数据
to create some some records here I'll
在这里创建一些记录
say steam dot of let's get some names my
说我们的名字叫蒸汽点
name is Josh nice to meet you Julian
名字叫乔希很高兴认识你朱利安
hello buddy how are you
你好哥们你怎么样
Sara Sergey yeah okay um what's your
莎拉·谢尔盖（Sara Sergey）是的，嗯，你是什么人
name Lee how do you spell it
姓李你怎么拼的
Nelson Nelson like that okay nice to
纳尔逊·纳尔逊（Nelson Nelson）
meet you gusto what about you Eddie
见到你，你会怎么样Eddie
Phillip like this Oh like this very cool
菲利普像这样哦很像这样很酷
okay very good what about you buddy like
好的，很好，你的哥们怎么样
like our spring data okay we have a we
像我们的 spring data 一样，我们有一个
have a Derek there's a six who wants to
有一个德里克，有六个人想
be we need two more victims actually
难道我们实际上还需要两个受害者
let's see I just want to get the
让我们看看我只想得到
audience involved there we go
观众参与我们
it's better one more
好多了
[Music]
[音乐]
I'll just think of some names here my
我会在这里想到一些名字
Dora the letter and Oh God there we go
多拉的信，哦，上帝，我们去了
so nice mini girls room Nelson that's
这么漂亮的迷你女孩房间纳尔逊
not nothing so this is names okay names
没什么，所以这是名字好名字
dot map name and we want to create a new
点图名称，我们想创建一个新的
reservation passing a null for the ID
保留传递ID的null
mapping it like this and there's our
这样映射它，这就是我们的
reservation stream and for each one of
预订流，并针对每个
those I want to write it to the database
那些我想写到数据库的东西
all say map or dot for each other or
都说彼此的地图或点或
this deposition pause about say if
这个沉积停顿一下
passing on that and there we go those
通过那，我们去那些
are react there's our nonreactive but
有反应，这是我们的反应迟钝，但
super fast code let's run this and see
超级快速的代码，让我们运行它，看看
what we get
我们得到什么
well I need the configuration oh yes so
好吧，我需要配置哦，是的，所以
so I'm gonna take these information here
所以我要在这里获取这些信息
there you go
你去
I see people taking photos yeah so
我看到人们在拍照
there's my cosmos DB instance right it's
这是我的cosmos数据库实例
called this is the native database name
称为本地数据库名称
here's the URI and there's the the key
这是URI，还有密钥
and you can get that by going into of
你可以通过进入
course your your your a copy of portal
培训您的门户副本
okay okay
好吧好吧
cosmos DB going to your instance and
宇宙数据库去您的实例和
then you go to your keys and you're
然后你去找钥匙，你就
given a primary key and a secondary key
给定一个主键和一个辅助键
okay so I'm just using the primary key
好吧，所以我只是使用主键
you get the URI and a key and you plug
您将获得URI和密钥，然后插入
that in and then here we run make sure
在那然后我们运行确保
obviously in a normal application
显然在正常应用中
you wouldn't store this stuff in your
您不会将这些东西存储在您的
property file you use it the vault yeah
您使用它的属性文件库是的
right so you use the constant goofy or
对，所以您使用恒定的高飞或
spring cut config server or the config
弹簧切割配置服务器或配置
vault the vault key value volts on Azur
在Azur上存储金库关键值伏特
and that will store the keys and values
它将存储键和值
separate from the application and then
与应用程序分离，然后
you can just inject them you can just
你可以注入它们，你可以
say a dollar sign my property name okay
说一个美元符号我的财产名称可以
so now there's a product well a lot of
所以现在有很多产品
products whoa okay how do you do limits
产品太好了，您如何限制
anybody know how to do a limit in sequel
任何人都知道如何限制续集
server is it just limit okay cosmos
服务器是限制宇宙吗？
so top like that okay let's try that out
这样的顶部好吧，让我们尝试一下
fingers and eyes crossed cool I was
手指和眼睛交叉，我很酷
awesome thank you okay so that worked
太好了，谢谢，好了，这样就可以了
and now we can go back to this Cosette
现在我们可以回到此珂赛特
saved we say find all that for each so
拯救了，我们说找到每个都这样
dot map okay actually I'm gonna say that
点图好吧，实际上我要说
for each let me just get all the records
对于每个，让我只获取所有记录
back and we just log it out so and walk
返回，我们就这样注销并步行
for gate that's fine we got two more
登机口还可以，我们再来两个
demos
演示
life is good so here we go there's our
生活是美好的，所以我们去那里是我们的
reservations from cosmos TV there's our
来自宇宙电视台的预订有我们的
data from sequel server now I'm using
我正在使用来自续集服务器的数据
the sequel data stores here that's fine
续集数据存储在这里很好
a very common thing when we build a
当我们建立一个
student system of course is you're not
学生系统当然不是
just doing synchronous reads and writes
只是做同步读写
you want to actually decoupled the
你想真正解耦
system especially when you move to the
系统，尤其是当您移至
cloud and when you decouple systems
云和解耦系统时
what's the easiest way to do that
最简单的方法是
exactly and so there's actually a really
确实，所以实际上有一个
interesting sort of branch of work
有趣的工作分支
that's being done at Microsoft being
这是在微软做的
lent being led in part by a gentleman
由绅士部分领导
named Clement masters just he's all he
他被任命为克莱门特大师
walks on the AMQP specification just
仅遵循AMQP规范
absolute genius mad scientist guy he
绝对是天才的疯狂科学家
works at he works on AMQP and he does a
在他从事AMQP工作期间，
lot of work with Microsoft and so the
与Microsoft进行了大量合作，因此
messaging support for Microsoft is just
对Microsoft的邮件支持只是
amazing some of the best in the business
令人惊叹的一些行业最好的
because this this crazy guy just
因为这个疯子只是
brilliant guy work sign right so so
才华横溢的人工作标志，所以如此
there's this message press the option
有此消息按选项
called
叫
event bus or service bus service buses
事件巴士或服务巴士服务巴士
as they were service bus is that right
因为他们是服务巴士就对了
and and that speaks multiple protocol so
并且说多种协议，所以
you can actually use it from a mqp
您实际上可以通过mqp使用它
you can use it from JMS you can use it
您可以从JMS使用它，也可以使用它
from a number of different API services
来自许多不同的API服务
most critical well today yeah yeah
今天最关键的是
there's a API binding that allows you to
有一个API绑定可以让您
talk to it through an EP you
通过EP与您交谈
if executed if you want yeah you can use
如果执行，如果您愿意，可以使用
Cupid which gives you a JMS binding so
为您提供JMS绑定的丘比特
there's a lot of options there or you
那里有很多选择，或者你
can just use the native the API and
可以只使用本地API
that's fine so that's what we're gonna
很好，这就是我们要做的
do is we're gonna use the Neve sort of a
要做的是我们将使用Neve
API here so I'm going to create a class
这里的API，所以我要创建一个类
a service bus demo and what I'm gonna do
服务巴士演示以及我要做什么
is I'm gonna right I'm gonna register a
是我要注册我要注册
listener wait a second because it takes
收听者稍等片刻，因为它需要
some time for the server to actually
服务器实际需要一些时间
recognize that I've been a listener and
认识到我一直是一个听众，
then I'll register I'll then I'll send
然后我将注册，然后我将发送
some data okay so private final I topic
一些数据还可以，所以我是私人决赛
I need to actually bring in the depends
我需要带进依赖
here so we go back to this palm that XML
在这里，我们回到XML
and we're gonna add in Azure service bus
我们将添加Azure服务总线
spring blue starter there we go okay
春天蓝色启动器，我们可以
that seems okay to me so we now we're
对我来说似乎还可以，所以我们现在
gonna say private final I topic clients
我会说私人决赛我主题客户
and private final I subscription client
和私人最终I订阅客户端
okay
好的
and event listener application ready
和事件监听器应用程序就绪
event public void service bus okay so in
事件公共无效服务巴士还可以，所以
this if you are if you know about AMQP
如果您对AMQP了解的话
if you know about random queue for
如果您知道随机队列
example then this model for service bus
例子然后这个服务总线模型
will look very familiar the reason is
看起来会很熟悉，原因是
because it's got the same arrangement
因为它有相同的安排
same topology as rabbitmq as as a as a
与Rabbitmq具有相同的拓扑
AMQP broker so you have this idea of a
AMQP经纪人，所以您有这样一个想法
destination which is where you send
发送目的地
messages but those messages don't you
消息，但那些消息不是你
don't send it directly to the queue or
不要将其直接发送到队列中，或者
to the topic you send it to something
到主题发送到某事
called an exchange in rabbitmq or in mqp
在Rabbitmq或mqp中称为交易所
panels and the same thing exists here so
面板和相同的东西在这里存在，所以
you have this you have this idea of I'm
你有这个，我有这个想法
gonna send it to this destination and
要发送到这个目的地，
then I have a I have a thing called a
然后我有一个我有一个叫做
subscription which hangs off of that so
挂在那里的订阅
the producer sends it to one thing the
生产者将其发送给一件事
consumer consumes from another okay
消费者从另一个可以消费
they're not they're not a sonic JMS
他们不是他们不是声音JMS
where producer and consumer talk to the
生产者和消费者交谈的地方
same queue or same topic etc so this
相同的队列或相同的主题等
thought I taught I subscript in client
以为我教客户下标
that register message handler new
注册消息处理程序新
iMessage handler
iMessage处理程序
I like that it's got eyes this is write
我喜欢这是写的眼睛
net you know we can see that code so
净，您知道我们可以看到该代码，因此
completel future that
完善的未来
[Music]
[音乐]
whatever no okay I don't care about that
不管怎么样，我不在乎
um I'm gonna do this I'm just gonna log
嗯，我要这样做，我要登录
the message right unhand oh I need a
信息不正确哦，我需要一个
exception throw his exception and when
异常抛出他的异常以及何时
the message arrives I'm gonna log out
消息到达我要注销
the message
讯息
okay so log4j log that info new message
好的，所以log4j记录该信息新消息
message dot get content type with
消息点获取内容类型
correlation ID message get correlation
相关性ID消息获取相关性
ID and body message dot okay oh I needed
ID和正文消息点好吧，我需要
to make that a string because it's just
制作一个字符串，因为它只是
bytes so it's it's a it doesn't care
字节，所以这是一个无关紧要的
about how you represent the data okay so
关于如何表示数据好吗
there's my thing okay and log dot error
我的事情还可以，并且日志点错误
exception and then finally once that's
例外，然后一旦那是
done registering I'll sleep one second
完成注册后我会睡一秒钟
and I'll send a message
我会发个信息
so this dot I taught a client dot send
所以我教客户发送的这个点
now how do we send the message as who
现在我们如何以谁的身份发送消息
are application it might be yeah there's
是应用程序可能是的
new message good stuff good stuff that's
新消息好的东西好的东西
exactly what it should be
到底应该是什么
hello at instant dot now all right let's
你好在即时点现在好吧，让我们
try that out
试试看
two minutes let's just say three minutes
两分钟，我们只说三分钟
it's fine nobody's gonna die okay so we
很好，没人会死的，所以我们
need configuration oh yes fair enough
需要配置哦，是的，足够公平
everything um so yeah properties service
一切都很好，所以物业服务
bus
总线
good stuff okay okay so here we're going
好东西好吧好吧，所以我们要走了
to you know got a connection string
你知道有一个连接字符串
you've got a topic name and you've got a
您有一个主题名称，并且有一个
subscription name these are two
订阅名称这是两个
different things or sending messages to
不同的东西或发送消息到
a topic you're subscribing from the
您正在订阅的主题
subscription okay
订阅还可以
and new message North correlation ID
和新消息北相关性ID
null and body hello equals hello aunt
null和身体问好等于你好阿姨
whatever okay so there's our consumer
没关系，所以有我们的消费者
now we're able to decouple obviously in
现在我们可以在
a normal program you wouldn't send a
普通程序，您不会发送
message to yourself that would be
给自己的信息是
ridiculous
荒谬
you'd have to producer to consumer but I
你必须从生产者到消费者，但是我
wanted to show you that and now at this
想告诉你，现在在这个
point I've got you know I got this I've
我知道你知道我知道了
got a a regular traditional thing that I
我有一件普通的传统东西
could have done without a zero like
本来可以做到没有零
sequel server I've had thing that's
续集服务器，我有那件事
completely unique to us or like like
完全是我们独有的或喜欢
cosmos TV I've got a thing that is made
宇宙电视台我有一个人造的东西
better by the fact that azores the
更好的是，亚速尔群岛
distributed cloud that has regions in
区域中存在区域的分布式云
every world part of world like Kozma
世界上每个世界的一部分，例如科兹马
like service bus taking advantage of a
像服务巴士一样利用
globally distributed engine network that
全球分布式引擎网络
messaging subsystem benefits from that
消息传递子系统从中受益
distribution and now finally if I've got
分配，现在终于有了
all these moving pieces I've got all
所有这些动人的东西
these things in the cloud all these
这些东西都在云端
things running in spring and they're
东西在春天运转，它们是
talking to each other I've got micro
互相交谈我已经微
services abound I'm gonna need some
服务比比皆是，我需要一些
operational yeah I'm gonna monitor that
是的，我要监视
I'm gonna have a lot of moving parts a
我会有很多活动部件
lot of confusing pieces so what I want
很多令人困惑的碎片，所以我想要什么
to do is I wanna be able to kind of
我想做的是
follow the movement of data in the
跟随数据的移动
system so how do you what do you
系统，那么你怎么样
recommend for that insight application
为该洞察力应用程序推荐
inside sorry ooh I am not used to your
内心抱歉，哦，我不习惯你
match windows
匹配窗口
yeah so inside it's a full moon solution
是的，所以里面是满月解决方案
if you use something like to reduce it's
如果您使用类似的减少方法，
kind of the same thing but it's all
有点一样，但全部
Aussie by Azure so you have nothing to
澳大利亚的Azure，让您无所事事
do to use it and we're good
做它，我们很好
bootephant sides so this is going to
boot面，所以这将
give you lots of tiny graph of your
给你很多你的小图
absolute by default what's good is that
绝对默认情况下，好的是
there's an integration or service screen
有一个集成或服务屏幕
boot so there's also a spinet starter I
开机，所以我也有一个小启动器
don't know where you put all your status
不知道你把所有身份放在哪里
oh yeah XML
哦，是的XML
this is that c-come on
这是c来
see let's give them that chef's touch
看看让我们给他们厨师的感觉
I'm here but he used Mac for years
我在这里，但他使用Mac已有多年
yes he's gone to the window no but I
是的，他去了窗户，不，但是我
will come back to a Mac pretty soon get
将很快回到Mac
back next week nobody yeah we fixed a
下周返回没有人，是的，我们修复了一个
version because yeah so what's going to
版本，因为是的，那会发生什么
happen is that as a support of
发生的是，作为对
micrometer with it so in the next word
千分尺
is yeah you will have you know
是的，你会知道的
micrometer is the new shiny which won't
千分尺是不会发光的新光泽
sing from spring boots right and so it's
从 spring boot 唱歌吧，所以
being to still matrix for cash for the
仍然是现金的矩阵
data source for Europe well everything
欧洲的数据源
then you get some sort of API for that
然后您会获得某种API
right
对
and so what is that spring would I was
那我那年春天是什么
going to send show micrometer also data
要发送显示千分尺也数据
to come inside boots inside that inside
进入里面的靴子里面
at this part
在这一部分
there okay I need a binky didn't we
那好吧，我需要一个笨蛋，不是吗
already did it
已经做了
no you do it okay so I'm gonna get the
不，你可以，所以我要
key from here this is a key thing to
从这里开始这是关键
choose in the future right because it's
选择将来的权利，因为它是
Jamaica later okay good I'm also hoping
牙买加以后还好，我也希望
we could push the key right
我们可以向右推钥匙
okay so localhost universe of to
好吧，所以本地主机的宇宙
ourselves all that so I said too much in
我们自己，所以我在
service it can take a little time for
服务可能需要一点时间
students to give the data okay I'm
学生们给我数据吧
making relicensing refund yeah it's
进行授权退款是的
going to assume that you can click on
假设您可以点击
live matrix then nobody everything works
实时矩阵，那么没人管用
well yes good yeah there we go so you
好，是的，很好，我们去了，所以你
don't need to it so you click again if
不需要它，因此如果您再次单击
you click again you should see them
再次单击，您应该看到它们
arrive in straightaway
马上到达
which is fun okay so I'm driving traffic
很好玩，所以我在增加流量
on the left you can see it arrival and
在左侧，您可以看到它的到来，
right already my friends I hope you got
现在我的朋友们我希望你能
something out of this get us it's better
这样做可以使我们更好
than you think so much for coming
比你想的要来的多
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]